beechnut.com 2013-11-11

# Beech-Nut Baby Food

|  |   
---  
| You Are Here: Home > Web > 20131111005941id_ > Http%3A >  > Www.beechnut.com > Terms  
---  
This is the web site of Beech-Nut Nutrition Corporation (“Beech Nut”).  
  |    
Our postal address is  
Beech-Nut Nutrition Corporation  
One Nutritious Place  
Amsterdam, NY 12010  
  |    
We can be reached via [email](http://bnhelpline.milnot.com/) or you can reach us by telephone at 1-800-BEECH-NUT (1-800-233-2468).  
  |    
This policy covers information collected by Beech Nut through its web site, [www.beechnut.com](http://www.beechnut.com/).  
  |    
   
**Beech-Nut Nutrition® Beech-Nut & Beech-Nut Goya New Pouches Giveaway**   
**OFFICIAL GIVEAWAY RULES (“OFFICIAL RULES”):**   
**Beech-Nut Nutrition**

NO PURCHASE NECESSARY. A PURCHASE WILL NOT INCREASE YOUR CHANCES OF WINNING. All federal, state and local laws and regulations apply. Void where restricted or prohibited by law.

**1\. ELIGIBILITY:**  The Beech-Nut Nutriti **on® “** **Beech-Nut & Beech-Nut Goya New Pouches** **”** Giveaway (the “Giveaway”) is open to individuals 18 years of age or older as of date of entry who are residents of the 50 United States. Employees of Beech-Nut Nutrition®/Hero®, (“Sponsor”), and each of their respective affiliates, subsidiaries, employees, dealers, distributors, retailers, advertising agencies, production agencies, electronic media firms, and their immediate family members and those living in the same household are not eligible to receive a prize. Each entrant agrees to be bound by and acknowledge compliance with these Official Rules.

**2\. PROMOTION PERIOD:** Giveaway begins at 9:00PM (EST) on November 9, 2013 and ends on November 30th. (the “Promotion Period”).  All entries must be submitted by 11:15:59PM (EST) on November 30th. Sponsor’s computer is the official time keeping device for the Giveaway.

**3\. HOW TO ENTER:** To enter, visit [www.facebook.com/BeechNut](http://www.facebook.com/BeechNut) and click “Like” to become a Beech-Nut Nutrition® fan and obtain access to the Giveaway. Then leave a comment on the page titled “New Pouches”. If you are already a Beech-Nut Nutrition® fan, you may enter the Giveaway by clicking the Giveaway tab and then submitting a comment on the page about Beech-Nut’s new pouches. Entrants agree to be bound by and acknowledge compliance with these Official Rules including the eligibility and entry requirements. Limit one entry per person during the Promotion Period. A selected recipient may be asked to provide Sponsor with proof that the selected recipient is the authorized account holder of the e-mail address associated with the selected entry. If a dispute cannot be resolved, the entry will be deemed ineligible. Use of automated devices not valid for entry. Entries become the exclusive property of the Sponsor and will not be returned. Sponsor may at its sole discretion disqualify anyone who violates the rules or undermines the integrity of the Giveaway by disabling cookies, using any form of automatic entering, or any other form of manipulation.

**4\. PRIZES:** **10 comments will be randomly selected from the “New Pouches” page on Beech-Nut’s Facebook to receive a prize package of Beech-Nut materials (prizes as listed on Facebook)**. Odds of receiving a prize depend on the number of entries received. No more than the advertised number of prizes will be given away. Limit of one prize per household. Prize recipients will be notified via Facebook and asked to provide their mailing address promptly. Prizes will automatically be shipped to the address provided by entrant. Any prize returned as undeliverable will be given away to an alternate. Sponsor is not responsible for any loss or damage to prizes incurred during shipment.

**5\. GENERAL RULES:** Entrants agree to be bound by these Official Rules and the Sponsor’s decisions. By submitting an entry in the Giveaway (i.e., by commenting in the new pouch Facebook page), you acknowledge and agree that Sponsor shall be permitted to use your entry data for marketing purposes on social media channels consistent with Sponsor’s privacy policies (available at [http://www.beechnut.com](http://www.beechnut.com/)) and applicable law. By accepting the Beech-Nut prize basket, recipients agree that the Sponsor and those acting under the Sponsor's authority may use recipients' names, pictures/portraits likenesses and/or voices, for advertising and promotional purposes worldwide in perpetuity without further consideration, unless prohibited by law. Recipients may be required to execute and return an Affidavit of Eligibility, Liability Release and (where legal) Publicity Release within fourteen days of issuance of notification. Prizes are non-transferable and no substitutions or cash redemptions will be made. Sponsor reserves the right to substitute a prize of equal or greater value in the event of unavailability. Any and all taxes are the recipients’ sole responsibility. Entries will not be acknowledged or returned.

BY ENTERING THE GIVEAWAY OR ACCEPTING ANY BEECH-NUT PRIZES, ENTRANTS AGREE TO INDEMNIFY, RELEASE AND HOLD HARMLESS SPONSOR, SPONSOR’S AGENTS AND AGENCIES, FACEBOOK AND EACH OF THEIR RESPECTIVE PARENTS, SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES, ADVERTISING AND PROMOTION AGENCIES (TOGETHER “AGENCIES”), AND EACH OF THEIR RESPECTIVE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, REPRESENTATIVES AND AGENTS FOR ANY AND ALL LIABILITY, CLAIMS OR ACTIONS OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER FOR ANY INJURY, LOSS OR DAMAGES OF ANY KIND TO PERSONS, INCLUDING DEATH, AND PROPERTY, DUE IN WHOLE OR IN PART, DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY, THAT MAY ARISE IN ANY WAY, FROM THE ACCEPTANCE, POSSESSION, USE OR MISUSE OF ANY BEECH-NUT PRIZES RECEIVED OR PARTICIPATION IN THIS GIVEAWAY OR PARTICIPATION IN ANY GIVEAWAY OR RELATED ACTIVITY. Sponsor shall not be responsible for any errors in these Official Rules or otherwise in any materials available at [www.facebook.com/BeechNut](http://www.facebook.com/BeechNut). If for any reason the Giveaway is not capable of running as planned, including due to infection by computer virus, bugs, tampering, unauthorized intervention, fraud, technical failure, human error or any other causes beyond the control of Sponsor that corrupts or affects the administration, security, fairness, integrity, or proper conduct of the Giveaway, Sponsor reserves the right in its sole discretion, to disqualify any individual who tampers with the entry process, and to cancel, terminate, modify or suspend the Giveaway and give away prizes from among all eligible entries received prior to cancellation or termination. Sponsor and Agencies are not responsible for lost, late, misdirected, illegible, postage-due or damaged entries or Internet technical, hardware, software, telephone or transmission failures of any kind, which limit a person’s ability to enter the Giveaway. Sponsor and Agencies assume no responsibility for any error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, communications line failure, theft or destruction or unauthorized access to, or alteration of, entries. The Sponsor and are not responsible for any problems or technical malfunction of any telephone network or lines, computer online systems, servers, or providers, computer equipment, software, failure of any e-mail or entry to be received by Sponsors on account of technical problems or traffic congestion on the Internet or at any web site, any combination thereof, or otherwise, including any injury or damage to entrant's or any other person's computer related to or resulting from participation or downloading any materials in the Giveaway. CAUTION: ANY ATTEMPT BY AN ENTRANT TO DELIBERATELY DAMAGE ANY WEB SITE OR UNDERMINE THE LEGITIMATE OPERATION OF THE GIVEAWAY MAY BE A VIOLATION OF CRIMINAL AND CIVIL LAWS AND SHOULD SUCH AN ATTEMPT BE MADE, SPONSORS RESERVE THE RIGHT TO SEEK DAMAGES FROM ANY SUCH PERSON TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.

Any and all disputes, claims, and causes of action arising out of or in connection with the Giveaway shall be resolved individually, without resort to any class action. This Giveaway shall be governed by, and construed in accordance with, the laws of the State of New York, regardless of conflicts of laws principles. Any action or litigation concerning this Giveaway shall take place exclusively in the federal or state courts sitting in New York County, New York, and each recipient expressly consents to the jurisdiction of and venue in such courts and waives all defenses of lack of jurisdiction and inconvenient forum with respect to such courts. Each recipient agrees to service of process by mail or other method acceptable under the laws of the State of New York. ANY CLAIMS, JUDGMENTS, AND/OR AWARDS OF ANY ENTRANT SHALL BE LIMITED TO ACTUAL OUT-OF-POCKET COSTS ASSOCIATED WITH ENTERING INTO THIS GIVEAWAY. EACH ENTRANT HEREBY WAIVES ANY RIGHTS OR CLAIMS TO ATTORNEY'S FEES, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ENTRANT, WHETHER FORESEEABLE OR NOT AND WHETHER BASED ON NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE.

**6\. Recipients:** For a list of recipients send a self-addressed, stamped envelope to: Beech-Nut Nutrition **® “** **Beech-Nut & Beech-Nut Goya New Pouches** **”** Giveaway Recipients List, 1 Nutritious Place, Amsterdam NY, 12010. Vermont residents may omit return postage.

**7\. SPONSOR:** **** The Giveaway is sponsored by Beech-Nut Nutrition®/Hero®, 1 Nutritious Place, Amsterdam NY, 12010.

Facebook is a registered trademark of Facebook, Inc. The Giveaway is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with, Facebook. You understand that you are providing your information to Beech-Nut Nutrition®/Hero® and not to Facebook. The information you provide will only be used in the event you are selected as a Giveaway recipient or if you have indicated that you would like to receive additional information from Sponsor.  

**Customer Information**  
  |    
We may require you to supply us with personal information during a registration process online prior to using certain features of our site (for example, prior to entering an online sweepstakes or receiving e-mail communications). If you choose to withhold personal data requested by us, it may not be possible for you to gain access to certain parts of the site or for us to respond to your query. We may also use the information provided in statistical form to understand our site’s demographics, such as percentage of male and female users, geographic location, age ranges, or a combination of these or other demographics. As detailed below, we will not share specific information about you to advertisers or third parties without your consent.

We may perform statistical analyses of aggregate (group) user behavior. This allows us to measure relative consumer interest in the various areas of our web site for product development purposes. Any information we collect is used for our own internal purposes to improve the content of the web site to enhance users’ experiences when visiting our site, to customize the content and/or layout of our pages, and to provide the services required by an individual user. We do not use personally identifiable information for any reason that is not disclosed either in this Policy or at the time the information is requested. Beech Nut processes personal data for specific and limited purposes, which we inform you about when we ask you for information. For example, we may collect and use personal data to provide you with products or services, to market products and services which we think may be of interest to you, or to communicate with you for other purposes. Beech Nut keeps your data only for as long as is reasonably needed for such purposes and in accordance with any applicable legal or ethical reporting or documentation retention requirements. Aside from an automatic reply to an e-mail received by us, it is our intent not to e-mail to you unless you request a particular service, or consent to being contacted by e-mail. There may be instances where you will have the opportunity to subscribe to an e-mail list that will send information about the site or our advertisers to your e-mail address, but after an initial mailing gauging your interest this will be continued only with your permission and consent.

We will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to 1) confirm to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process serviced on Beech Nut or the site, 2) protect and defend the rights or property of Beech Nut or its web site, and 3) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Beech Nut’s web site or the public.  
  
  |    
**Child Information**  
  |    
Beech Nut does not attempt to collect personal information from children. We cannot always determine if a user is a child. 

Beech Nut will not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal data from a minor under the age of 13 without obtaining prior consent from a person with parental responsibility (e.g., a parent or guardian) through direct off line contact. We will provide the parent with (a) notice of the specific types of personal data being collected from the minor, and (b) the opportunity to object to any further collection, use, or storage of such information, Beech Nut abides by laws designed to protect children.

Parent age data is collected to comply with COPPA regulations. The Beech Nut site is not intended for audiences under 13 years of age.

Users may choose to add their child’s name and/or picture onto the web site to enhance your personal site experience. Your child’s name and/or photo will not be sold to or shared with third parties or tracked and monitored by Beech Nut.  
  
  |    
**Web site Log Files**  
  |    
Web site log files are generated that collect the information about your computer hardware and software which may include your IP address, date, time and pages visited, browser type and referring web site addresses. Aggregate reports for web site visitors are generated that do not contain personally identifiable information other than the IP address.

An IP address is a number assigned to your computer when you connect to the Internet. As part of the protocol of the Internet, web servers can identify your computer by its IP address. In addition, web servers may be able to identify the type of browser you are using or even the type of computer.

Beech Nut collects IP addresses and related information for the purposes of system administration, to assess the traffic to our site, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to maintain and improve our site. We do not link IP addresses to your personally identifiable information. We can and will use IP addresses, however, to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our terms of service or to protect our service, site, customers or others.

Web site log files are only used to generate internal reports about various areas of the Beech Nut site and to maintain quality of service.   
  
  |    
**Cookies**  
  |    
Internet cookies may be used in several places on the Beech Nut site. They may be used in the message board area to keep track of individual users’ previous visits. Cookies may also be used in certain contest and voting areas of the Beech Nut site to make sure users don’t enter/vote more than allowed.

Cookies are small bits of information that some web sites (including the Beech-Nut web site) transfer to an individual’s hard drive for research purposes. Beech Nut may use cookies to analyze the traffic, such as total visitors and pages viewed on our site, and make improvements based on the data we collect. Beech Nut never saves passwords or credit card information in cookies. The use of cookies has become a standard in the industry, especially at web sites that provide any kind of personalized service.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can usually set your browser to refuse cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you refuse cookies, you may not be able to use some of the functionality of the Beech Nut site. Cookies may also be used by Beech Nut’s advertisers and partners from third party sites to which the Beech Nut site links. We do not control these cookies. The use of cookies by advertisers is standard in the Internet industry.  
  
  |    
**Who Is Collecting This Information**  
  |    
Beech Nut collects this information via our web site. In the case of co branded sites, various third parties may collect such information. You should review the applicable privacy policies of these third parties before providing personally identifiable information. Beech Nut is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.  
  |    
**Links to Other Sites**  
  |    
While you are using Beech Nut’s web site, you may be linked or directed to other third party sites outside the Beech Nut site that are beyond Beech Nut’s control. For example, you might click on a link or banner ad that will take you off Beech Nut’s site. Each of these third parties may have a privacy policy different from that of Beech Nut. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. You should review the applicable privacy policies of these third party sites before providing personally identifiable information. These links and banners may take you to sites of advertisers, sponsors and co branding partners. Please review the privacy policies of these sites. Beech Nut is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

PLEASE BE AWARE that when you voluntarily disclose personal information (such as your name or e-mail address) in chat areas or bulletin boards or to third parties, that information may be collected by others outside our control and may result in unsolicited messages from others.  
  
  |    
**Mailing Lists**  
  |    
Beech Nut maintains mailing lists. Subscribers may opt out of those lists at any time. User information may be kept to determine winners in contests that are run on the Beech-Nut site and to mail out winning prizes, and to provide customized content. That information is used for no other purpose.   
  |    
**User Registration**  
  |    
  
Beech Nut does not require user registration to access content at this site, except for those wishing to interact with other fans on message boards.

If you have any questions about the privacy policy at beechnut.com, please e-mail Beech Nut at [beech-nut@beech-nut.com](mailto:beech-nut@beech-nut.com).

From time to time, this Privacy Policy may be updated. Your continued use of the Beech-Nut site following changes to these forms is acceptance of those changes. We encourage you to periodically review this Policy to be informed of how we are protecting your information. From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our web site periodically. Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by calling us at the number provided above, e-mailing us at the above address or writing us at the above address.

Upon request, we offer visitors the ability to correct inaccuracies in contact information and communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to the site. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us an e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number or writing to us at the above address.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.

« BACK TO TOP
